# **SUMMARY**

I'm a detailed people-first UX/Product Designer with six years of experience as a Product Manager. I excel at designing simple and effective solutions to complex user problems, relying on research and the company's business objectives to inform my decisions.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **UX/PRODUCT DESIGN FREELANCER**

New York, NY | March 2018-present UX research, strategy, information architecture, product design

Craft designs by applying design thinking principles throughout the design process to build empathic information architectures and prototypes.

- <u>HORTŪS</u>: a beauty salon in lower Manhattan. Created new logo & labels for custom products. Redesigned e-commerce website.
- <u>Bonbids</u>: redesigned the onboarding process fo a fundraising gamfication platform resulting in 90% increase in engagement.
- <u>Assemble</u>: Fully designed a cloud storage application that resolved frustrations users experienced with other applications.
- <u>Happy Time</u>: Fully designed an iOS application that filled a gap in the market and allowed users to find desired Happy Hours .

# DIRECTOR OF SALES MARKETING, SALES, AND COMMUNITY EXECUTIVE

Primary (Live Primary, LLC)  $\,|\,$  New York, NY  $\,|\,$  Aug. 2016-Dec. 2017 Coworking space with wellness amenities

Chosen as the company's first executive hire. Promoted to Director of Sales after demonstrating a strong ability to close deals and cultivate a strong community with a mix of established corporate companies (e.g., Pepsi), nonprofits (e.g., Kiva), and early-stage startups.

• Achieved 60% closure on leads and 93% office occupancy leading to a substantial increase in revenue.

#### PRODUCT MANAGER

babyMed | New York, NY | Sep. 2010-May 2016 One-stop online fertility and pregnancy resource

Developed and led an external team of developers, designers, and writers. Conducted usability testing and used findings to develop a taxonomy structure, content strategy, and full redesign.

 Increased pageviews 650% (to 12 million) and users 400% (to 2.75 million). All traffic was organic.

## **CASE PLANNER**

SCO Family of Services | New York, NY | Oct. 2007-Oct. 2011 Voluntary not-for-profit human service agency

Managed a caseload of high-risk young men aged 17-21 years-old living in a foster care group home.

# TOOLSET

#### **UX DESIGN SKILLS**

User Surveys
User Interviews
Competitive Analysis
User Stories & Flows
Information Architecture
Personas
Wireframing
Prototyping
Lo-Fi & Hi-Fi Mockups
Content Strategy
Typography
Color Theory
Branding
Usability Testing

#### **UX DESIGN TOOLS**

Sketch
Figma
Adobe Creative Suite
Invision
UsabilityHub
Maze
Balsamiq
Principle

## FRONT-END SKILLS

HTML/CSS Git/Github Javascript Bootstrap/UI Kit

## **EDUCATION**

CERTIFICATE, PRODUCT DESIGN Bloc | Online | 2018

**CERTIFICATE, TECHNICAL MARKETING**Startup Institute | New York, NY | 2015

CERTIFICATE, MEDIATION

Mediation Centre | Ontario, CA | 2010

BACHELOR OF ARTS, PSYCHOLOGY Pitzer College | Claremont, CA | 2007